Have you ever wondered on what specific foods you can eat to whiten your teeth?
Well my name is Michelle and I am a dental assistant with Solutionz and I am here to kind of give you a few choices to help whiten your teeth.
First of all, milk is always a great product to drink.
It helps strengthen your teeth, and in return it helps kind of to keep your teeth nice and white.
Chewing on apples, biting into apples, it kind of, the acid from it will break up any stainings that you might have and then also too, the rind of the apple will kind of clean your teeth also in the same sense when you are chewing on the apple it kind of frees of the bacteria and the debris that might be resting on your teeth.
Also too, lemons, if you cut up a lemon and kind of just rub your teeth with the lemon.
You do not want to do that too often because the acid from the lemon will actually eat away at your enamel and kind of maybe possibly expose your dentin and in return you will start to become sensitive to hot and cold temperatures.
So lemons every once in a blue moon basically, if you just cut up a lemon wedge, kind of chew on it for a little bit, rub your teeth on it.
And then also too, with taking whitening tooth paste.
But the main reasons, the types of foods that will help whiten your teeth are milk, drinking lots of milk, will actually whiten your teeth and keep them with the calcium and the strength of them.
And also too with lemons, but you do not want to do that too much, you also just want to do that in moderation.
But once again my name is Michelle and I am a dental assistant with Solutionz and hopefully I just explained to you the certain foods to eat to keep your teeth white.